

25, Bulgokbuk-ro, Bundang-gu, Seongnam-si, Gyeonggi-do, 13604, Rep. of KOREA

□ (+82) 10-2732-7793 | ■ tommy.dm.kim@gmail.com | ★ carrtesy@github.io | □ carrtesy | 🛅 dongmin kim

Summary

AI Researcher pursuing M.S Degree at KAIST (Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology).

BA in Global Economics and Computer Science at Sungkyunkwan University.

Research interests in Time-series Analysis and Anomaly Detection.

Publications

WaveBound: Dynamic Error Bounds for Stable Time Series Forecasting

New Orleans, USA

NeurIPS 2022

YOUNGIN CHO*, DAEJIN KIM*, **DONGMIN KIM**, MOHAMMAD AZAM KHAN, JAEGUL CHOO

• Regularization Technique for Time-series forecasting models • Publication Link: https://arxiv.org/abs/2210.14303

Residual Correction in Real-Time Traffic Forecasting

Atlanta, Georgia, USA

CIKM 2022

Daejin Kim*, Youngin Cho*, **Dongmin Kim**, Cheonbok Park, Jaegul Choo

- · Improving traffic models' performance using residual correction mechanism: modeling of failures
- Research project with Naver Maps Team, KAIST, UNIST
- Publication Link: https://dl.acm.org/doi/abs/10.1145/3511808.3557432

Education

M.S. IN ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE

Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST)

Daejeon, South Korea

Sept. 2021 - Present

• Academic Advisor: Jaegul Choo (GPA: 4.0/4.3)

Sungkyunkwan University

Seoul, South Korea

B.A. IN GLOBAL ECONOMICS AND COMPUTER SCIENCE

Mar. 2014 - Feb. 2021

• GPA: 4.32/4.5 (Global Economics: 4.19/4.5, Computer Science 4.47/4.5)

The Chinese University of Hong Kong Shatin, N.T., Hong Kong

EXCHANGE STUDENT

Fall Semester, 2019

Myungduk Foreign Language High School

Seoul, Korea

CHINESE DEPARTMENT Mar. 2011 - Feb. 2014

Work Experience _____

KT Corporation (Korea Telecom)

Gyeonggi-do, South Korea

June. 2021 - Aug. 2021

INTERN, SW ENGINEER

- Developed Topological Visualization Web-based application based on Log Data of Computing Infrastructures
- Project Github: https://github.com/carrtesy/KT_Genio_Topological_Visualization

Samil PwC Seoul, Korea

INTERN. RISK ASSURANCE TEAM Jan 2020 - Feb 2020 · Developed RPA service using Uipath and python

DONGMIN KIM · RÉSUMÉ JANUARY 3, 2023

Projects

Autopilot ProjectDaejeon, South Korea

RESEARCHER Mar 2022 – Present

- Autopilot project with ROK ADD (Agency for Defense Development, Republic of Korea)
- · Worked on Natural Language Processing Modules, especially Named Entity Recognition (NER) and Voice Recognition Module

Year-Dream School Project Seoul, South Korea

TEACHING ASSISTANT, LECTURER

Dec. 2021 - Mar. 2022

- Provided lectures on ML/DL, especially RNNs and Tree-based models
- Lecture materials can be found at: https://github.com/carrtesy/tommys-awesome-lectures

Crude Oil Price Prediction based on Gaussian Kernel Function Networks

Seoul, South Korea

Undergraduate Researcher (SKKU Undergraduate Dissertation)

Mar 2020 - Nov 2020

- Role: Dataset collection, model training, evaluations with Python (Advisor: Prof. Rhee Man Kil)
- Project Github: https://github.com/carrtesy/Oil-Price-Prediction-Project

Tensor Decomposition for Deepfake Detection

Seoul, South Korea

Undergraduate Researcher

July 2020 - Aug 2020

- Deepfake detection project using tensor decomposition algorithms, mainly TF Keras (Advisor: Prof. Simon Woo)
- $\bullet \ \, {\tt Project \, Github: https://github.com/carrtesy/Deepfake_with_tensor_decomposition}$

Networking System Laboratory

Seoul, Korea

Undergraduate Researcher

Aug. 2020 - Dec. 2020

• Packet Steering using SR-IOV, using Virtual NIC, Qemu, KVM (Advisor: Prof. Younghoon Kim)

Pet-caring Robot Project

Seoul, Korea

EMBEDDED SYSTEM PROJECT COURSE

Sep 2020 - Dec 2020

- Role: Sound Streaming, Bluetooth, Display Control, Motor Control, Humidity Sensor Control with C, Python
- $\bullet \ \, \text{Presentation Video: } \\ \text{https://drive.google.com/file/d/1-Zy1u3YFXNShyjKSyJK_40nSqBsFRG7h/view?usp=sharing} \\ \text{total presentation Video: } \\ \text{https://drive.google.com/file/d/1-Zy1u3YFXNShyjKSyJK_40nSqBsFRG7h/view?usp=sharing} \\ \text{https://drive.google.com/file/d/1-Zy1u3YFXNShyjKSyJKSyJK$

Xv6 Operating System Project

Seoul, Korea

OPERATING SYSTEM COURSE

Mar 2020 - June 2020

- Implemented Linux CFS Scheduling Algorithm, memory management, MMAP system call, Swap-in-and-out, File system extension using C
- $\bullet \ \, \text{Project Github:} \, \textbf{https://github.com/carrtesy/xv6_OS_build_project}$

Website Development Seoul, Korea

WEBSITE FOR SKKU FINANCE ASSOCIATION GLIF

Dec 2018 – Mar 2019

- · Developed and deployed websites using python Django and pythonanywhere
- Project Github: https://github.com/carrtesy/GLIF_Website_Project

Skills

Programming Python, Pytorch, Keras, C, C++, Linux, Django, Javascript

Tools Git, Docker, GCP

Languages Korean (Native), English (Fluent), Mandarin (Basics)

Hobbies Drum Playing, Weight Training, Basketball

Extracurricular Activities and others

SKKU Rock Band LCDA Seoul

DRUMMER *Mar.* 2014 - Dec. 2015

SKKU Financial Academic Association GLIF

Seoul, Korea

ASSOCIATION LEADER

June. 2018 - June. 2019

ROKAF Headquarter Gyeryong-si, Korea

AIRMAN OF INFORMATION SYSTEMS MANAGEMENT WING

Dec. 2015 - Dec. 2017

• Administrative Affairs, managing military records, supporting English translation of documents

JANUARY 3, 2023 DONGMIN KIM · RÉSUMÉ 2